Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
- Correspondence
  - 1934
    - Broo - Brot. (Box 40)
    - Broun, Heywood (Box 40)
    - Brow - Bru (Box 40)
    - Burgess, J. S. (Box 40)
    - Burns, Vincent G. (Box 40)
    - Buttrick, George A. (Box 40)
    - Buttrey, Adelbert J. (Box 40)
    - Cal - Car (Box 40)
    - Central Trades and Labor Council (Box 40)
    - Chaffee Family (Box 40)
    - Chalmers, Allan K. (Box 40)
    - Chal - Chap (Box 40)
    - Chicago Commons (Box 40)
    - Christian Endeavor World (Box 40)
      See also Davis, Bert H.
    - Christian C - Chur (Box 40)
    - Ci (Box 40)
    - Clark - Clarke (Box 40)
    - Clee, F. Ray (Box 40)
    - Cle - Cli (Box 40)
    - Colby, Bainbridge (Box 40)
    - Colg - Colt (Box 40)
    - Columbia University (Box 40)
    - Commission on Evangelism and Devotional Life (Box 40)
    - Committee on Militarism in Education (Box 40)
    - Committee on N. - Commu. (Box 40)
    - Conf - Cong (Box 40)
    - Connecticut College (Box 40)
    - Cons - Cool. (Box 40)
    - Cooperative League (Box 40)
    - Cope, Ellen (Box 40)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 41)
    - Cor - Cot (Box 41)
    - Cou - Cow (Box 41)
    - Croc - Croz (Box 41)
    - Cum - Cur (Box 41)
    - Danaher, Hortense (Box 41)
    - Dar - David (Box 41)
    - Davis, Bert H. (Box 41)
      See also Christian Endeavor World
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 41)
    - Davis T - W (Box 41)
    - Deb - Deu (Box 41)
    - Dinsmore, William W. (Box 41)
    - Dudley, William E. (Box 41)
    - Durant, Will (Box 41)
    - East Si - Eastern (Box 41)
    - Eddins, F. K., Jr. (Box 41)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 41)
    - Edi - Edu. (Box 41)
    - Ell - Elm (Box 41)
    - Emergency Relief Fund for Destitute and Unemployed (Box 41)
    - Epworth H - L (Box 41)
    - Erit, John B. (Box 41)
    - Essex Suburban Federation of Men's Bible Classes (Box 41)
    - Eva - Eve (Box 41)
    - Expositor, The (Box 41)
    - Fam - Fay (Box 41)
    - Federal Civil Works Administration (Box 41)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 7 folders (Box 41)
    - Federation of Churches of Rochester and Monroe County (Box 41)
    - Federation for Support of Jewish Philanthropic Society of New York City (Box 41)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, Inc., 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Feiker, Mabel (Box 41)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 10 folders (Box 41)
    - Fellowship of Socialist Christians (Box 41)
    - Ferguson, J. M. (Box 41)
    - Fis - Fiv (Box 41)
    - Fla - Flo (Box 41)
    - Fog - For (Box 41)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 41)
    - Fost - Fox (Box 41)
    - France, Melville J. (Box 41)
    - Fra - Fri (Box 41)
    - Gard - Garr (Box 41)
    - Gates, Goodrich (Box 41)
    - General D - S (Box 41)
    - Gille - Gillm (Box 41)
    - Gol - Gov (Box 41)
    - Grace House (Box 41)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Gree - Gru (Box 41)
    - Guh - Gul (Box 41)
    - Guthrie, William Norman (Box 41)
    - Gypson, Ward (Box 41)
    - Hall, Cameron P. (Box 41)
    - Hal - Ham (Box 41)
    - Hari - Hars (Box 41)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 41)
    - Hatch, Harold (Box 41)
    - Hawthorne, Reverend Walter T. (Box 41)
    - Hays, Will H. (Box 41)
    - Hea - Her (Box 41)
    - Hig - Hir (Box 41)
    - Hog - Holl (Box 42)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Horton, Reverend Douglas (Box 42)
    - Houck, Winton R. (Box 42)
    - Howa - Hows (Box 42)
    - Hug - Hull (Box 42)
    - Hum - Hunn (Box 42)
    - Hutchinson, Paul, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Ind - Int (Box 42)
    - Internation R - S (Box 42)
    - Jam - Jap (Box 42)
    - Jenney, Chester E. (Box 42)
    - Jenney, Ray Freeman (Box 42)
    - Jewish War Veterans (Box 42)
    - Joh - Joi (Box 42)
    - Jones, Edgar - Paul (Box 42)
    - Jones, Phillip - Josephson, Anna (Box 42)
    - Jui - Jun (Box 42)
    - Kaplan, Mrs. Rose (Box 42)
    - Keb - Kes (Box 42)
    - Kie - Kin (Box 42)
    - Kla - Klo (Box 42)
    - Knight, Walter David (Box 42)
    - Kop - Kos (Box 42)
    - Kraus Defense League (Box 42)
    - Kri - Kro (Box 42)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services (Box 42)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 42)
      - Budget Allocation of Funds, Finances, 5 folders (Box 42)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices, Responses, Arrangements for, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Contributions to Labor Temple, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Complaints, Supplies, Equipment, 7 folders (Box 42)
      - Programs and Activities, 8 folders (Box 42)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 4 folders (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Lack - Laco (Box 42)
    - Lad - Lar (Box 42)
    - Lea - Lei (Box 42)
    - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 42)
    - League of National Association, Inc. (Box 42)
    - Leat - Lei (Box 42)
    - Lic - Lis (Box 42)
    - Lindlof, Johanna (Box 42)
    - Lor - Low (Box 42)
    - Luccock, Emory W. (Box 42)
    - Luce, Henry R. (Box 42)
    - Lundquist, Alice (Box 42)
    - Lyman... (Box 42)
    - Lyon, Hiram W. (Box 43)
    - Mac C - Mac M (Box 43)
    - Mack - Madison House (Box 43)
    - Madison House Society - Mai (Box 43)
    - Man - Mar (Box 43)
    - Mas - Mat (Box 43)
    - Mc A - Mc G (Box 43)
    - Mec - Merril (Box 43)
    - Merritt - Met (Box 43)
    - Methodist-Episcopal Church (National, North, South), 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Metr - Mey (Box 43)
    - Michigan, University of (Box 43)
    - Minc - Minister's A (Box 43)
    - Minister's Union, 6 folders (Box 43)
    - Moh - Mor (Box 43)
    - Mot - Mou (Box 43)
    - Mooney, Tom (Box 43)
    - Morgenthau, Henry (Box 43)
    - Nagpada Neighbourhood House (Box 43)
    - N.A.A.C.P. National Civic Federation (Box 43)
    - National Conference of Jews and Christians (Box 43)
    - National Congress for Unemployed and Social Insurance - National Council for the Prevention of War (Box 43)
    - National Council Protestant-Episcopal Church - National Italian Evangelical Conference (Box 43)
    - National League for American Citizenship, Inc. - National Religion and Labor Foundation (Box 43)
    - National Unemployment League - National Urban League Natural Eyesight System (Box 43)
    - Near East Camp (Box 43)
    - Near East Foundation (Box 43)
    - New En. - New Er (Box 43)
    - New Deal - New Haven (Box 43)
    - New Jersey Joint Council on International Relations (Box 43)
    - New Leader, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Newark and New Jersey Annual Reports (Box 43)
    - New York American - New York City Conference on Worker's Education (Box 43)
    - New York (City of)
      - Board of Aldermen (Box 43)
      - C.C.N.Y. (Box 43)
      - Commissioner of Accounts (Box 43)
      - Commissioner of Parks Moses, Robert (Box 43)
      - Commissioner of Department Public Markets, Weights and Measures Morgan, William Fellowes, Jr. (Box 43)
      - Comptroller of Department of Finance (Box 43)
      - Cunningham, W. Arthur (Box 43)
      - Department of Public Welfare, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Department of Taxes and Assessments (Box 43)
      - Home Relief Bureau (Box 43)
      - Office of the Mayor LaGuardia, Fiorello (Box 43)
      - Office of the President of the Boroughts of Brooklyn-Queens (Box 43)
    - New York
      - Committee on the Use of Leisure Time (Box 43)
      - Conference Against War (Box 43)
      - Evening Post-Herald Tribune (Box 43)
      - I - Po (Box 43)
      - Protestant-Episcopal City Mission Society (Box 43)
      - Sc - So (Box 43)
    - New York State
      - Council of Churches and Religious Education (Box 43)
      - Federation of Labor (Box 43)
      - Labor Committee (Box 43)
      - State of (Box 43)
      - Governor, Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 43)
      - State Education Department (Box 43)
    - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association (Box 43)
    - New York U - W (Box 43)
    - Nich - Nico (Box 43)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 43)
    - Nixon, Reverend Justin (Box 43)
    - No Frontier News Service (Box 43)
    - No More War Parade (Box 43)
    - Nob - Nor (Box 43)
    - Nye, Gerald P. (Box 43)
    - Oberlin College (Box 43)
    - Ocean City Seashore Home for Babies (Box 43)
    - Oftendahl Einer (Box 43)
    - Ohio State University (Box 43)
    - Olm - Oly (Box 43)
    - Open Road, The (Box 43)
    - Osborne, Harold (Box 43)
    - Owen... (Box 43)
    - Pad - Pai (Box 43)
    - Page, Kirby, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Pal - Pare (Box 43)
    - Papazian, Bertha Sullivan (Box 43)
    - Parker, Fletcher Douglas (Box 43)
    - Parker, M - Pay (Box 43)
    - Peabody, George Foster (Box 43)
    - Peale, Norman Vincent (Box 43)
    - Pell, Mrs. F. Livingston, Jr. (Box 43)
    - Pendle Hill (Joseph O. Platt) (Box 43)
    - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of (Box 43)
    - Peoples’ Crusader, The (Box 43)
    - Pi (Box 44)
    - Precita Valley Community Center (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Advance (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 44)
      - Board of National Missions (Box 44)
      - Office of the General Assembly (Box 44)
      - Office of the Moderator (Box 44)
      - Synod of New Jersey (Box 44)
      - Synod of New York (Box 44)
      - Synod of Ohio (Box 44)
      - Synod of Tennessee (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Fellowship for Social Action (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Headquarters Minnesota (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Theological Seminary of Chicago (Box 44)
    - Presbyterian Union of Cleveland (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of Chicago Church Extension Board (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of Cincinnati (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of Dayton (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of Detroit (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of the Hudson Young People's Christian Union (Box 44)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Bartlett, Maitland Stated Clerk (Box 44)
      - Committee on Evangelism (Box 44)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 44)
      - Emergency Relief Fund (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 44)
      - Savage, Theodore E., Executive Secretary, 6 folders (Box 44)
      - Social Service Commission (Box 44)
      - Special Committee of Presbytery (Box 44)
    - Pric - Pro (Box 44)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 44)
    - Rad - Rat (Box 44)
    - Read, Ralph H. (Box 44)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 44)
    - Ref - Rei (Box 44)
    - Revell Company, Fleming H. (Box 44)
    - Rhoad, Frank T. (Box 44)
    - Rid - Riv (Box 44)
    - Richards, George H., 7 folders (Box 44)
    - Rob - Ros (Box 44)
    - Rub - Rut (Box 44)
    - Rybicki, Edward C. (Box 44)
    - Sad - Say (Box 44)
    - Sch - Sco (Box 44)
    - Schieffelin, Bayard (Box 44)
    - Schieffelin, Mrs. William Jay (Box 44)
    - Schieffelin, William Jay (Box 44)
    - Schroeder, Theodore (Box 44)
    - Sea - Set (Box 44)
    - Sha - Shu (Box 44)
    - Simkhovitch, Mrs. V. G. (Box 44)
    - "Singer of Psalms" Management (Box 44)
    - Skinner, E. B. (Box 44)
    - Smith, A - W (Box 44)
    - Soc - Sou (Box 44)
    - Society for the Advancement of Judaism (Box 44)
    - Sockman, Ralph W. (Box 44)
    - Spe - Spr (Box 44)
    - Sta - Stel (Box 44)
    - Stewart (Box 44)
    - Stillman, Mrs. Ernest G. (Box 44)
    - Stitt, Reverend Jesse William (Box 44)
    - Stockdale, George M. (Box 44)
    - Stone, Abraham (Box 44)
    - Stone, Mrs. Lewis (Box 44)
    - Stover, Charles B., Memorial Association, Inc. (Box 44)
    - Strong, Sydney (Box 44)
    - Stud - Stuy (Box 44)
    - Sub - Sur (Box 44)
    - Swaim, J. Carter (Box 44)
    - Swope, Gerard, See Simkhovitch, Mrs. V. G.
    - Tar - Tay (Box 44)
    - Tea - Techni (Box 44)
    - Technocracy, Inc. (Box 44)
    - Ten - Tes (Box 44)
    - Thea - Thet (Box 44)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 44)
    - Thom - Thou (Box 44)
    - Tioga Community Forum (Box 44)
    - Toastmaster’s Club (Box 44)
    - Trag - Trav (Box 44)
    - Tuc - Tur (Box 44)
    - Uesugi, Sumio (Box 44)
    - Unif - Union Se (Box 44)
    - Union Theological Seminary
      - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 44)
      - Curry, Bruce (Box 45)
      - General File (Box 45)
      - Gould, Ivan M. (Box 45)
      - Mabon, James B. (Box 45)
      - Maurer, Harry A. (Box 45)
      - Swift, Arthur L., Jr. (Box 45)
      - Webber, Charles C. (Box 45)
    - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, 4 folders (Box 45)
    - United States Government (Box 45)
    - Unit - Univ (Box 45)
    - Van - Vau (Box 45)
    - Verkey, Stanley (Box 45)
    - Vil - Vis (Box 45)
    - Wai - Wal (Box 45)
    - War Resisters League
      - Hugan, Jessie Wallace (Box 45)
      - Kaufman, Abraham (Box 45)
      - Others (Box 45)
    - Ward - Warr (Box 45)
    - Web - Wef (Box 45)
    - Weid - Weis (Box 45)
    - Welfare Council of New York City (Box 45)
    - Well - Wes (Box 45)
    - Whe - Whi (Box 45)
    - Who's Who Among Association Executives (Box 45)
    - Wig - Wil (Box 45)
    - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 45)
    - Woe - Wom (Box 45)
    - Women's Peace Union (Box 45)
    - World Alliance for International Friendship Through the Churches (Box 45)
    - World Fellowship of Faiths (Box 45)
    - World Tomorrow, The (Box 45)
    - Wou - Work (Box 45)
    - Wright, C - T (Box 45)
    - Wylie, H. W. (Box 45)
    - Yale (Box 45)
    - Yea - Yer (Box 45)
    - Youn - Yout (Box 45)
    - Y.M.C.A. Various Branches, 8 folders (Box 45)
    - Y.W.C.A. Various Branches, 5 folders (Box 45)
  - 1935
    - Abyssinian Baptist Church (Box 45)
    - African Welfare Committee (Box 45)
    - Adams, B W (Box 45)
    - Ald - Alp (Box 45)
    - American Birth Control League, Inc (Box 45)
    - American Christian Committee for German Refugees (Box 45)
    - American Ch - Ec (Box 45)
    - American Eugenics Society (Box 45)
    - American Federation of Labor (Box 45)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 45)
    - American League Against War and Fascism (Box 45)
    - American League Youth (Box 45)
    - Anth - Anti (Box 45)
    - Arg - Art (Box 45)
    - Associated W - Association for (Box 45)
    - Auburn Theological Seminary Campus (Box 45)
    - Bailey, Boyd L. (Box 45)
    - Bailey, Mrs. George R. (Box 45)
    - Barnes, George Emerson (Box 45)
    - Barnes, Roswell P., Bates College (Box 45)
    - Battle, George Gordon (Box 45)
    - Bea - Ber (Box 45)
    - Big - Bis (Box 45)
    - Bla - Blo (Box 45)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 45)
    - Bra - Bron (Box 45)
    - Broo - Brow Bu (Box 45)
    - Cadman, S. Parkes (Box 45)
    - Cal - Car (Box 45)
    - Central C - P (Box 45)
    - Chaffee, Family of (Box 45)
    - Chalmers, Allen Knight (Box 45)
    - Cham - Chic (Box 46)
    - Chil - Christian Am. (Box 46)
    - Christian Century, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Christian Citizenship Council (Box 46)
    - Chronicle of World Affairs (Box 46)
    - Churchman, The (Box 46)
    - Ci (Box 46)
    - Clarke, K - W (Box 46)
    - Coffin, Henry S. (Box 46)
    - Coll - Colu (Box 46)
    - Commi - Commu (Box 46)
    - Conf - Cong (Box 46)
    - Conn. Coll. - Conn. Cong. (Box 46)
    - Connecticut Council of Churches and Religious Education (Box 46)
    - Connecticut State (Box 46)
    - Conse - Consu (Box 46)
    - Cope, Ellen (Box 46)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 46)
    - Correlated Enterprises (Box 46)
    - Cou - Cov (Box 46)
    - Cow - Cur (Box 46)
    - Dartmouth Union (Box 46)
    - Davis, Chester M. (Box 46)
    - Davis, Jerome, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Daviso - Day (Box 46)
    - Department of Religious Radio (Box 46)
    - Dic - Dir (Box 46)
    - Dod - Dou (Box 46)
    - Dudley, Reverend William (Box 46)
    - Eastern States Cooperative League (Box 46)
    - Economic Planning and Social Engineering League (Box 46)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 46)
    - Edi - Edu (Box 46)
    - Eleazer, R. B. (Box 46)
    - Elliot, J - P (Box 46)
    - Emergency Committee for Striker’s Relief (Box 46)
    - Emergency Peace Campaign, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - Essel - Essex (Box 46)
    - Evang - Evans (Box 46)
    - Exe - Exp (Box 46)
    - Fam - Far (Box 46)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 9 folders (Box 46)
    - Federation of Christian Women (Box 46)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies (Box 46)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 7 folders (Box 46)
    - Ferrero-Sallitto Defense Conference (Box 46)
    - Fisher, Ruby (Box 46)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 46)
    - Foreign Affairs Forum (Box 46)
    - Fra - Fre (Box 46)
    - Fric - Frie (Box 46)
    - Furnald, Henry N. (Box 46)
    - Gad - Gar (Box 46)
    - Gilman, Mrs. Edith (Box 46)
    - Gol - Gov (Box 46)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Gree - Grol (Box 46)
    - Group Theatre, Inc., The (Box 46)
    - Guthrie, William Norman (Box 46)
    - Hall - Hals (Box 46)
    - Hark - Harris, C. (Box 46)
    - Harris, P - Harrison (Box 46)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Har - Haw (Box 47)
    - Heb - Her (Box 47)
    - Hill, Reverend George A. (Box 47)
    - Hill School (Box 47)
    - Hollister, J. H. (Box 47)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 47)
    - Holz - Hosk (Box 47)
    - Hor - How (Box 47)
    - Hud - Hut (Box 47)
    - Ins - Inter R (Box 47)
    - Intern C - L (Box 47)
    - International Missionary Council (Box 47)
    - International R - S (Box 47)
    - Iowa State Traveling Men’s Association (Box 47)
    - Jenney, Ray F. (Box 47)
    - Jewish Welfare Board (Box 47)
    - Jones, John Paul (Box 47)
    - Kim - Kiw (Box 47)
    - Kla - Kli (Box 47)
    - Knox, Herbert W. (Box 47)
    - Kra - Kre (Box 47)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services (Box 47)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 47)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices, Responses, Arrangement for, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Contributions to Labor Temple, Appeals, Responses, Thank You Notes, 6 folders (Box 47)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 5 folders (Box 47)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment (Box 47)
      - Programs and Activities, 8 folders (Box 47)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - Lackland, George S. (Box 47)
    - Lai - Lav (Box 47)
    - Leag - Lek (Box 47)
    - Leber, Charles T. (Box 47)
    - Lei - Lev (Box 47)
    - Lid - Lip (Box 47)
    - Loc - Low (Box 47)
    - Lyon, Reverend James (Box 47)
    - MacRury, Reverend J. Allison (Box 47)
    - Mai - Matt (Box 47)
    - Maverick, Maury, Congressman (Box 47)
    - Mc A - Mc De (Box 47)
    - Mc Do - Mc N (Box 47)
    - Med - Mer (Box 47)
    - Methodist-Episcopal Church
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 47)
      - Board of Home Missions (Box 47)
    - Methodist Federation for Social Service (Box 47)
    - Metropo D - Y (Box 47)
    - Mile - Milli (Box 47)
    - Miner, Theodore (Box 47)
    - Ministers' Union of America (Box 47)
    - Minneapolis Committee of One Hundred (Box 48)
    - Minnesota State Conference and Institute of Social Work (Box 48)
    - Minu - Mis (Box 48)
    - Mod - Moh (Box 48)
    - Mol - Moor (Box 48)
    - Morr - Moth (Box 48)
    - Moti - Mou (Box 48)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 48)
    - Myers, Orel J. (Box 48)
    - Nastasi, Samuel (Box 48)
    - National Ch - Nat. Com. for (Box 48)
    - Nat. Com. on - Nat. Conf. of (Box 48)
    - Nat. Cong. - Nat. Or. (Box 48)
    - National Religion Labor Foundation, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Nat. Tr - Nat. Un (Box 48)
    - Natu (Box 48)
    - Nea - Nel (Box 48)
    - New D. - New J. (Box 48)
    - New York City
      - Am - Bi (Box 48)
      - Ba - Chi (Box 48)
      - Christian Endeavor Union (Box 48)
      - Congregational Association (Box 48)
      - Mission Society (Box 48)
    - New York (City of)
      - Board of Education (Box 48)
      - Board of Estimates (Box 48)
      - C.C.N.Y. (Box 48)
      - Commissioner of Accounts, Blanshard, Paul (Box 48)
      - Department of Health (Box 48)
      - Department of Public Welfare (Box 48)
      - Emergency Home Relief Bureau (Box 48)
      - Office of the Mayor, La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Box 48)
      - Police Department (Box 48)
    - New York Co - T (Box 48)
    - New York State
      - Council of Churches and Religious Education (Box 48)
      - Federation of Labor (Box 48)
    - New York (State of)
      - Assembly Chamber (Box 48)
      - Division of Military and Naval Affairs (Box 48)
      - The Governor, Lehman, Herbert E. (Box 48)
    - New York T - Ub (Box 48)
    - New York Un - Yo (Box 48)
    - Nicol, Reverend James and family (Box 48)
    - Niebuhr, H. Richard (Box 48)
    - No M - Non (Box 48)
    - Northfield League (Box 48)
    - Northfield S. - Ny (Box 48)
    - Oberlin College (Box 48)
    - O'Connor, John J., Congressman (Box 48)
    - Oli - Olm (Box 48)
    - Open Road, The (Box 48)
    - Order of Corinthians (Box 48)
    - Osborne Association, Inc., The (Box 48)
    - Our - Out (Box 48)
    - Page, Kirby, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Pan - Pap (Box 48)
    - Park - Pars (Box 48)
    - Partlow, John D. (Box 48)
    - Payne, Franklin R. (Box 48)
    - Pea - Pei (Box 48)
    - Pell, Mrs. F. Livingston, Jr. (Box 48)
    - Pen - Peo (Box 48)
    - Phillips, Wilbur (Box 48)
    - Pie - Pio (Box 48)
    - Play of the Month Club (Box 48)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 48)
      - Board of National Missions and Board of of Foreign Missions, 6 folders (Box 48)
      - Board of Pensions (Box 48)
      - Office of General Assembly (Box 48)
      - Office of General Assembly Committee of Five, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Publicity Department (Box 48)
      - Synod of New York (Box 48)
      - Synod of Ohio, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Presbyterian Fellowship for Social Action (Box 48)
    - Presbyterian Minister's Fund for Life Insurance (Box 48)
    - Presbyterian Tribune (Box 48)
    - Presbyterian Union of Cleveland (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of Chicago Church Extension Board (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of Cincinnati (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of Dayton (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of the Hudson (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of Minneapolis Church Extension Board (Box 48)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Bartlett, Maitland, Stated Clerk (Box 48)
      - Committee on Spiritual Advance (Box 48)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 49)
      - Savage, Theodore E., Executive Secretary, 4 folders (Box 49)
      - Social Service Committee (Box 49)
      - Special Committee of Presbytery (Box 49)
      - Union of New York City (Box 49)
    - Quinn, Elmer F., Senator (Box 49)
    - Rac - Rat (Box 49)
    - Rec - Rel (Box 49)
    - Rhoad, Reverend Frank T. (Box 49)
    - Richards, George H., 4 folders (Box 49)
    - Richie, Frank (Box 49)
    - Ril - Rio (Box 49)
    - Robinson, C - J (Box 49)
    - Roc - Rom (Box 49)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President (Box 49)
    - Rou - Roy (Box 49)
    - Russel, R - S (Box 49)
    - Rutgers University (Box 49)
    - Rybicki, Edward C. (Box 49)
    - Sag - Saw (Box 49)
    - Schacht, Robert H. (Box 49)
    - Schieffelin, Bayard (Box 49)
    - Schieffelin, William Jay (Box 49)
    - Schil - Schm (Box 49)
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln (Box 49)
    - Scientific Colonization League (Box 49)
    - Sha - She (Box 49)
    - Sib - Sic (Box 49)
    - Siddal, Marion (Box 49)
    - Simkhovitch, Mary K. (Box 49)
    - Sippola, R. W. (Box 49)
    - Skinner, David (Box 49)
    - Sloan, Eleanor (Box 49)
    - Smith, F - R (Box 49)
    - Soc - Son (Box 49)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 49)
    - Stan - Stat (Box 49)
    - Stauffer, Milton T., New Brunswick Theological Seminary (Box 49)
    - Stee - Stev (Box 49)
    - Stew - Ston (Box 49)